Finding Aid for the Program for Art on Film Records, 1951-1999, undated IA20008
Institutional Records and Archives
- Records collected by the Program for Art on Film, 1951-1998; undated; (bulk 1984-1994); Series II.; 51.8 Linear Feet; (45 boxes, 3 framed posters, 2 flat files)
  - Information on films, 1974-1996; Series II.C.; 3 Linear Feet; (5 boxes)
    - Golub, 1988; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - A Good Time to be West, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Les Grandes Expositions, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Grant Wood's America, 1983; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Happiness of Still Life: Scenes - From the Austrian Biedermeier, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Havana Postmodern: the New Cuban Art, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Herman Melville: Damned in Paradise, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Homage to Chagall, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Howard Finster: Map of Visions, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Humanities Through the Arts, 1983 (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - The Hutterites, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Images, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Imago, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Imago Urbis, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - In a Brilliant Light: Vincent Van Gogh in Arles, 1985 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Innovation Series, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Isenheim, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Islands, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Jack Levine, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Jan Cox: A Painter's Odyssey, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Jean Renoir, The Boss, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Je Suis Fou, Je Suis Mechant: Autoportrait de James Ensor, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Joan Mitchell, Portrait of an Abstract Artist, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Joseph Beuys: Transformer, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Kathe Kollwitz, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - The Killing Detail, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Kids of Survival, 1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Kokoschka, Errinnerung (Rememberance), 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Lady Jane, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Laura Gilpin: An Enduring Grace, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Le Corbusier, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Legacy with Michael Wood, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Leonardo's Deluge, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Lights and Shadows, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Louise Bourgeois, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Lyman H. Howe's High Class Moving Pictures, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Made in Milan, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Maya Lin, 1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Memories of Monet, 1984 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Michelangelo Pistoletto: I Have a Mirror, You Have a Mirror, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Michelangelo: Self Portrait, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - The Moderns, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - My Left Foot, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Le Mystère Picasso, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Mystery of the Master Builders, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Name of the Rose, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Naturaleza Viva, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Naturally Creative, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - New Ways of Seeing: Picasso, Braque and the Cubist Revolution, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - New World Visions, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - No War-No Peace, 1985 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Nouveaux Réalistes, Les, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - 100 Masterworks from Great Museums, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Orpheus and Eurydice, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Other Side of the Moon, The, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Painter's World, The, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Painting the Town, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Palettes, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Panoply of Ghana, 1984 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Paul Cadmus: Enfant Terrible at 80, 1984 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Paya et Talla, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Permeke, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Philip Pearlstein, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Picasso and Braque: Pioneering Cubism, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Picasso: A Painter's Diary, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Pablo Picasso: The Legacy of a Genius, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Portrait of Imogen, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Post No Bills, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Potters at Work, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - The Precious Legacy, 1985 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Pride of Place, 1985 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - The Primal Mind, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Primary Colors, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Quality of Light, A, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Quest of Jimmy Pike, The, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - A Question of Attribution, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Ranch, 1985 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Rembrandt, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Red Grooms: Sunflower in a Hothouse, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Resident Alien, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Return to Glory: Michelangelo Revisited, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Rikyu, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Robert of Iron, 1987-1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Saint-Gaudens: Masque of the Golden Bowl, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - The Shakers, 1985 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Shock of the New, 1981 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Signals series, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Sister Wendy, 1997 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Skyline: Chicago, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Smithsonian World, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Sorceress, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Spaces: The Architecture of Paul Rudolph, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - The Spirit in Architecture, 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - The Stations of Bach, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - State of the Art, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Strokes of Genius, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Style Wars, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Suleyman, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Superstar, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Taj Mahal, 1983 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Tant Que le Monde Sera, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - The Third Dimension, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Tibet: A Buddhist Trilogy, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - To Orpheus, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Tous les Matins du Monde, 1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Travels, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - The Tribal Eye, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Turner's Genius, 1985 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Van Gogh, 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Vienna 1900, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Vincent and Theo, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Vincent: The Life and Death of Vincent van Gogh, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Vincent van Gogh: Der Weg Nach Courrieres, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Vision on Art, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Visions, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Voices and Visions, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Voyage, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Walker 'Round Sculpture, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Welcome to the Water Planet, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - With Paint on Canvas, 1981 (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
    - Woman: Who is Me?, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
    - Zed and Two Noughts, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-27A)
  - Information on film-related conferences, 1982-1997; Series II.D.; 0.25 Linear Feet; (5 boxes)
    Records consist of catalogs, brochures, press releases, clippings, photographs, printed materials, and correspondence, collected by the Program for Art on Film, 1969-1997, that describe conferences where films on art were screened. Much of the material is promotional in nature (catalogs, brochures, and press releases). The bulk of the records are printed materials; any correspondence found within the records contextualizes these records, and is often in response to a direct query by Program for Art on Film personnel. Some of the information was used to compile the Art on Screen ("Critical Inventory") database.
    - American Association of Museums:
      - AAM Media and Technology, 1993-1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-113)
      - AAM, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-113)
      - AAM MUSE Videos, 1994-1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-113)
      - [AAM MUSE, 1996 and 1997; AAM MUSE, 1995; Museum Living Room, 1991, 1992, 1993, 1994], 1991-1997 (Box 2004.IA.14-113)
      - AAM Museum Living Room Schedule, 1982-1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-1A)
      - AAM Museum Film Programs, 1987; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-1A)
    - Originals for packets, Boston, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-94)
    - Sound and Images: Research (articles, books, etc.), undated (Box 2004.IA.14-94)
    - Sound and Images final notes, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-94)
    - Sound and Images (University of Southern California) Handout materials, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-94)
    - [AAM meeting transcripts, 1993, 1991; other meeting transcripts; musical performances; AIVF general meeting transcripts; Sound and Images (4 tapes)], undated (Box 2004.IA.14-85B)
    - [AAM meeting transcripts, 1993, 1991; other meeting transcripts; musical performances; AIVF general meeting transcripts; Sound and Images (4 tapes)], undated (Box 2004.IA.14-85C)
  - Subject Files, 1973-1998; Series II.E.; 10 Linear Feet; (12 boxes)
    These records are listed in general subject order (subject files and film reviews), and in alphabetical order.
    Records consist of correspondence, clippings, articles, printed matter, press releases, memos, notes and reports collected by the Program for Art on Film, 1965-1998, as research material for Program for Art on Film publications and projects, and titled "Subject Files". The records describe artists, films, organizations, projects, art historical time periods and movements, and such diverse topics as art education, attitudes towards films, international television markets, and management.
    For additional information on films, see Series II.C. Information on films.
    - Subject files:
      - Abstract Expressionism, 1986; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Academy Awards, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-11A)
      - Aesthetics [empty folder], undated (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Africa, 1986; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Against the Odds, 1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Animation, 1986-1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Anthropology, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Arab Films, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Archaeology, 1973; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Archaeology, 1989; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Archives, Film and T.V., 1990; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-11A)
      - Architecture: Articles/Bibliographies, etc., 1990-1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-11A)
      - Architecture, 1997 (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Architecture, 1985-1994; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Art Education, 1984-1991; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-11A)
      - Art Education, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-11A)
      - Art Exhibits, 1986-1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-11A)
      - Art Forgeries, 1987; 1992,; 1997,; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Art Information Sources, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-11A)
      - Art General, 1993-1996; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Art Productions (Winnie File), 1986-1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-11A)
      - Artists, 1985-1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Art Therapy [empty folder], undated (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Articles, 1983-1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-59A)
      - Asian American Films, 1992-1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Asian American Films, 1997 (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Asian Art, 1987-1988; 1993-1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Australian Aboriginal Art, 1988; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Australian Films, 1985-1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Avant-Garde Films, 1984 (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Articles: Art, Artists, Exhibitions, 1987-1989; (2 folders) (Box 2004.IA.14-11A)
      - Articles: Art and Film [I], 1984-1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-11A)
      - Articles: Art and Film [II], 1973-1986; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-11A)
      - Articles: Art and Film [III], 1991-1992; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-11A)
      - Articles: Art, Artists, Exhibitions, 1986-1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-11A)
      - Articles: films, 1986-1989; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-11B)
      - Articles: French Culture/France, 1989; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-11A)
      - Articles: Getty Museum, 1989-1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-11A)
      - Articles: Japan/Japanese Culture, 1988-1989; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-11A)
      - Arts and Technology, 1986-1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-11A)
      - Attitudes to Films, 1986; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-11A)
      - Audience Research: Xeroxes Museum Audiences, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-11A)
      - Audio Cassettes, 1986-1987; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-11A)
      - Awards, 1984-1985 (Box 2004.IA.14-11A)
      - "Background Notes" Research, 1989; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-11A)
      - Bibliographies, 1981-1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-11A)
      - Bibliographies, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-11B)
      - Black and Hispanic Art Museums, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-11B)
      - Black Artists, 1983-1985; 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Black Cinema, 1988; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Blake, William, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Book Arts, 1985-1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - British TV, 1987-1989; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-11B)
      - Captioned Films, 1988-1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-11B)
      - Cartoons, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-11B)
      - Cascade Vertical Landscapes, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
      - Cataloga, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
      - Censorship, 1984-1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-11B)
      - Chagall, Marc, 1986; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Children's Films, 1985; 1988,; 1996,; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Chinese Films, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Cinema Studies, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Cinematographers, 1986; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-11B)
      - Cites: Cine Exhibition: La Villette '87, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-11B)
      - Cities, 1988-1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - City Films, 1990-91, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Collectors, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Colorization Controversy, 1986-1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-11B)
      - Comics, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Computer Animation, 1989-1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-11B)
      - Computer Art, 1990-1991; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Conservation, 1993; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Copyright Issues, 1989-1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-11B)
      - Country Homes, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
      - Craft Films, 1991; 1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
      - Crafts, 1992-1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Creativity, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
      - Cubism, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
      - Czechoslovakia, 1965-1967; 1974-1975,; 1977-1978 (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
      - Dali, Salvador, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
      - Dance, 1986; 1995,; 1997 (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
      - Decorative Arts, 1973; 1985 (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
      - Edgar Degas, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
      - Delacroix, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
      - Design, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
      - Digital Image Processing, 1987-1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
      - Distribution Services, 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
      - Drawing, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
      - Dream of Light, 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
      - Dreams, 1985 (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
      - Dutch Films, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Dutch Films, 1984-1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
      - Educational fairs [fair use guidelines], 1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
      - Egypt, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
      - Ethnographic Films, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - European T.V., 1987-1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
      - Exhibition: info file, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
      - [Experimental films: Film culture @ Tramway brochures], undated (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
        [Loose in box, but labeled "Experimental films".]
      - Fakes and Forgeries, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Fashion/Costume, 1986; 1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Feature Films, 1988; 1992,; 1994,; 1997 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Feature Films on Art, 1978 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Fiber Arts [empty folder], undated (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Films as Art, 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Film Consultants, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
      - Film Music, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
      - Film Preservation, 1986; 1988-1989,; 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
      - Film Reviews, 1984; 1987-1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
      - Films by Photographers, 1991; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Finnish Films, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Flowers and Gardens, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Folk Art, 1986; 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - French Films, 1985 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - French Information: General, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
      - French Information: Video, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
      - Funding Info., 1987-1988; 1998 (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
      - Futurism, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Gaudi, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - German Films, 1985-1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - German Films, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - German Information: Television, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
      - Glass, 1993; 1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Government and the Arts, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
      - Goya, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Graphic Arts (Calligraphy, Book Illuminations, etc.), 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Greek Films, 1990; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Graphic Design, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Guggenheim Panel on Art and TV, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
      - High Definition Television and Video, 1987-1990; 1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
      - Hispanic American Artists, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - History, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Historic Preservation, 1991; 1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Home Video, 1988-1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - Image Processing, 1988; 1992,; 1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - "India!", 1985 (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - Indian Films, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Input, April 4-12, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - Interactive Multimedia, 1989; 1992,; 1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - International Film Organizations, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - International TV Markets, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - International TV Markets/Festivals, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - Irish Films, 1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Italian Films, 1985-1986; 1990,; 1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Japanese Films, 1988; 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Jewish Films, 1992-1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Labs-Film/Video, 1991-1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - Landscape Architecture, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Latin America, 1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Latin American Art, 1984 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Latin American Films, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Leonardo da Vinci [empty folder], undated (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Libraries and Videos, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - Literature, 1987; 1990,; 1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Subj file: Literature and Film, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Subject file: Management, 1991-1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - The Matenadaran, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Media Business News, 1988-1989; 1993-1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - Medialog, 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - Microfiche, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - Middle East, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Miscellaneous articles, 1987; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-11B)
      - Miscellaneous Film Info., 1986-1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - Miscellaneous Film Info., 1983-1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - Miscellaneous Films (Asian, African), 1988-1992; 1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Miscellaneous Shorts, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Motion Pictures: History, 1968-1969 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Multi-Cultural, 1992; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Multi-Media, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - Murals, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Museums and Computers, 1984-1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-11B)
      - Museum Productions, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Museums, 1986; 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Museums and Films: research on, Nov '91, 1983; 1988-1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - Subject file: Music, 1986; 1993-1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Music, 1990-1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Music Video, 1986-1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Naive Art, 1990; 1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Native American, 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Native American Artists, 1993-1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - NEA Controversy/Helms, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - New Technologies, 1984-1985 (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - New York, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - NYC Arts Info: Misc., 1994-1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - Nordic Television (Scandinavia), undated (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - Omax/Showscan, 1985-1987; 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - Obituary, 1997 (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - Obituaries, 1988-1997 (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - Obituaries, 1993-1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - Obituaries, 1990-1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - Online Services: Arts, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - Onto, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
      - Open University, 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-62A)
      - Optical Disk Pilot Info., 1986; 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - Outsider Art, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Painting, 1992-1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Panels, Conferences, Etc., undated (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - People, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - Performing Arts, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Perspective [empty folder], undated (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Photo Sources, 1984 (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - Photography, 1985; 1988-1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Photography Workshops, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - Picasso, 1980 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Politics and Art, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Pre-Colombian, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Primitive Art, 1989-1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Prints and Drawings, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Production Services, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - Public Art, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Publications, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-57B)
      - Puerto Rican Films, 1987-1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Q, 1991-1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-59A)
      - Quilts, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - R, 1986-1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-59A)
      - Religion and Art, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Renaissance and Baroque Art, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Rodia, Simon, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Romanesque Art, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - S, 1987-1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-59A)
      - Science and Art, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Sculpture, 1986-1987; 1990,; 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-62B)
      - Short Films, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-56A)
      - "Sightlines: Journal of the American Film and Video Aasociation" issues, 1984; 1988,; 1990,; 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-41)
      - Spanish Cinema (empty), undated (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Spanish Artists, 1987-1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-56A)
      - Spanish Language Films, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-56A)
      - Stained Glass, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Surrealism, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-47)
      - Swedish Films, 1986-1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-56A)
      - T, 1984-1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-59A)
      - Technology and Art, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-56A)
      - Television, 1985-1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-11B)
      - Texas, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-56A)
      - Tribal Arts, 1983 (Box 2004.IA.14-56A)
      - Trains, 1988; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - U, 1988-1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-59A)
      - V, 1985-1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-59A)
      - Venice, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-56A)
      - Video, 1983-1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-11B)
      - Video Art, 1984-1998 (Box 2004.IA.14-56A)
      - Video Art, 1985; 1987-1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-56A)
      - Video Art, 1991; 1993,; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-23)
      - Video Out, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-59A)
      - Video Pool Inc., 1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-59A)
      - The Video Project, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-59A)
      - Video Tours, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-59A)
      - Videographe, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-59A)
      - Videotakes, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-59A)